<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.1.2//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.1.2/docbookx.dtd">
<article lang="">
  <para><note><remark>HTML: &lt;meta http-equiv="X-UA-Compatible" content="ie=edge"&gt;</remark></note><link linkend="">Home</link> <olink targetdocent="">Couples</olink> </para>
  <para>Rebecca Spear,</para>
  <sect1>
    <title>MA, AMFT #121560</title>
    <para>I am an Associate Marriage Family Therapist:</para>
    <para>Supervised by Dr. Melissa Springstead Cahill, PsyD, MFT #47113</para>
    <para>Private Practice: Anchor Children and Family Counseling, Inc., Pasadena, CA</para>
    <para>Supervised by Dr. Lori Tyler, PhD, M.O.B.; Clinical Psychologist PSY20342Intern at the Kieffer E. Franz Clinic of the C. G. Jung Institute of Los Angeles , CA</para>
    <sect2>
      <title>Welcome to my psychotherapy site. Compassionate understandingand care are nearby.</title>
    </sect2>
    <sect2>
      <title>I work in the holistic psychodynamic traditions of Carl G. Jung andanalytical psychology to compassionately assist you in releasingnegative patterns which have outgrown their usefulness.</title>
    </sect2>
    <sect2>
      <title>I work with children, adolescents, couples, andfamilies. Click on the tabs to see how I use differenttherapeutic modalities with my clients.</title>
    </sect2>
    <sect2>
      <title>Through evidence-based interventions from brain research andneuroscience I utilize Depth Psychology, Brainspotting (BSP),Somatic Experiencing (SE), Mindful Awareness Practices (MAPS),Dream Analysis, and your own creative spark in NarrativeTherapy and Art Therapy to unlock your true potential inbecoming the unique self you are meant to be.</title>
      <para>
        <ulink url="mailto:%20DepthHealer@gmail.com">DepthHealer@gmail.com</ulink>
      </para>
      <para>
        <olink targetdocent="tel:%20213-640-6068">213-640-6068</olink>
      </para>
      <para>Schedule your free consultation</para>
      <para>Serving greater Los Angeles</para>
      <sect1 id="img1">
        <para>
          <inlinegraphic fileref="#Pictures//Becky%2010.jpg" width="0.7862inch" depth="0.3929inch"/>
        </para>
      </sect1>
      <sect1 id="img2">
        <para>
          <inlinegraphic fileref="#Pictures//Persephone.jpg" width="0.7862inch" depth="0.3929inch"/>
        </para>
      </sect1>
      <para>Persephone,-Rebecca Spear</para>
    </sect2>
  </sect1>
</article>
